That's right, Ringo.
そうよ リンゴ
This is...
これが
Destiny!
運命なんだから
ええ
Tabuki... isn't here?
多蕗さんが
いない
くるくる回る
<< kurukuru mawaru kimi no hitomi >>
<< Round and round, your eyes wander around >>
君の瞳探して回る
<< sagashite mawaru eki no home >>
<< Searching around the station's platforms >>
駅のホーム
<< hibiku fanfare >>
<< The sound of fanfare from afar >>
響くファンファーレ
ガラガラ音を立てる街
<< garagara oto wo tateru machi >>
<< The clamorous city making noise >>
とりあえず耳を貸してみたの
<< toriaezu mimi wo kashite ita no >>
<< I tried to keep an ear out for all this >>
もうすぐ消えるはずの世界に
<< mousugu kieru hazu no sekai ni >>
<< In a world that's about to end >>
御免ね
<< gomen ne >>
<< I'm sorry >>
もう二度と会えないようなそんな気がして
<< mou nido to aenai youna sonna ki ga shite >>
<< I just had a feeling I would never see you again >>
運命が笑う
<< unmei ga warau >>
<< Fate is laughing at us >>
臨界点突破してんだ
<< rinkaiten toppa shiten da >>
<< I'm already past the point of no return >>
限界なら既に去って
<< genkai nara sude ni satte >>
<< Far over my limit >>
絶対的支配だって
<< zettaiteki shihai datte >>
<< Even your absolute control has >>
崩壊
<< houkai >>
<< Crumbled >>
終末理論は机上の空論でしかないって
<< shuumatsu riron wa kijou no kuuron shika naitte >>
<< "The end of the world is nothing but a hypothesis" >>
ゼロとイチの世界線の果てから
<< 0 to 1 no sekaisen no hate kara sakebu yo >>
<< Is what I'm crying out from other side of the binary world line >>
叫ぶよ
もうすぐ君が会いにくるような気がして
<< mou sugu kimi ga ai ni kuru you na ki ga shite >>
<< I have a feeling you'll come see me soon >>
僕は目を閉じるよ
<< boku wa me wo tojiru yo >>
<< So I will be waiting with my eyes closed >>
You look really sleepy today.
随分眠そうですね 先生
Oh, it's just you, Takakura.
何だ 高倉か
You caught me being a goofball.
間抜けなとこ見られちゃったな
You must be tired with all the preparations for the wedding.
やっぱり結婚の準備とか何かと忙しいんですよね
No, it's something else.
いや それとは別でね
I just had a hell of a night.
昨日の夜は大変だったんだよ
Hell of a night?
大変って まさか床下の方から何か出て来た とか
Don't tell me...
Did something crawl up from under the floor?
Under the floor? What are you talking about?
床下 って 何のこと
By "hell of a night,"
昨日の夜は大変って
you mean an adult night?
アダルトな夜だったってこと
Don't be ridiculous, Bro!
な…何言ってんだよ 兄貴
いいや だったらいいんだけどね
I wish that was the case.
ひゃー 本当はファビュラスマックスだったんでしょ
Admit it. It was Fabulous Max, wasn't it?
Come on, Takakura. We're in school!
おい おい ここは学校だぞ 高倉
Please give my baby brother a good lesson, teach.
先生 お子様の弟にご指南よろしくお願いしますよ
んじゃ
Later.
Oh, see you tomorrow.
あ また明日
The birds look really agitated today.
それにしても 今日は鳥たちが騒ぐな
So, what happened last night?
で 先生 昨日の夜って
Why are you so interested?
何だ やけに食い付くな
や ただのマンションの水漏れなんだけどね
Well, it was just a plumbing problem in the condo.
百合に急に呼び出されて 二人で大慌てさ
Yuri called me out at night. It was a huge ruckus!
But I'm glad our new place didn't get ruined.
でも せっかくの新居が台無しにならなくてよかったよ
新居
New place?
はい これ
Here you go.
Yuri's the only one who's moved in already,
まだ百合しか住んでないけど
落ち着いたら リンゴちゃんと遊びに来てよ
but come visit us with Ringo when we settle down.
We moved!
と言っても 僕も今日引っ越しだから
Actually, I'm moving in today too,
We moved!
so maybe you don't really have to wait!
意外と早く招待できるかも
The movers I hired are probably at work now!
今頃業者の作業も進んでる頃かな
Impossible...
嘘よ
This can't possibly happen.
こんな事あるわけが
Are you ready to give up now?
これで諦めがついたろう
Starting today, Tabuki and Yuri will be...
今日から多蕗と百合さんが
Impossible.
嘘よ
こんな事あるわけが
It can't happen.
いい加減現実見ろよ
Snap out of it!
Tabuki won't be coming back here.
多蕗はここにはもう帰って来ない
嘘よ
Impossible.
運命日記か何か知らないけど
I don't know if this is the Fate Diary or whatever,
こんな事 あるわけが
This can't happen...
You can keep scheming and fantasizing,
君がどんなに画策しょうが妄想しょうが
but what's impossible is impossible!
駄目な物は駄目なんだよ
ううん そんなはずないのよ
This can't be happening.
This diary...
この日記は
This diary represents...
この日記はあたしと桃果の
Momoka and my...
もう帰ろう
Let's go home.
You have to clean up your stuff under the floor.
床下の荷物を片づけなきゃいけないだろう
I'll help you out again.
また手伝うからさ
Um, I hate to say this, but...
あの こんなこと言うのなんだけど
You should have a healthier romantic relationship next time.
次は真ともな恋愛した方がいいんじゃないかな
Your mom will be worried if you keep doing dangerous stuff.
危険な事してると お母さんも心配するよ
Don't touch that.
それに触らないで
This is a special diary.
この日記は特別なの
The fate prophesied by it...
予言された運命が外れるなんてこと ありえないんだから
can never be wrong.
Must be tough to have your heart broken.
失恋って 大変だなぁ
Tokikago Yuri Announced Engagement
Retires from the troupe.
先日 婚約と歌劇団引退を同時に発表された時籠百合さんですが
Ms. Yuri Tokikago announced her engagement and retirement on the same occasion few days ago.
One, two, one, two.
Her national tour starting from Osaka tomorrow will mark the end of her career.
明日 大阪から始まる全国ツアーが最後になるということで
It appears the phone calls by her disappointed fans are pouring into the opera company...
トップスターの引退を知るファンの取り合わせが
I was a fan of hers. Isn't that disappointing, Threetie?
ファンだったのに 残念だね 三ちゃん
So, you're saying you can't carry out Operation Marriage Blues?
じゃ 例のマリッジブルー作戦は無理だって言うんだな
What marriage blues? Didn't you see how lovey-dovey he was acting?
マリッジブルーどころか 見たろう
あの多蕗の惚気っぶり
That was no way to act in front of students!
生徒に見せる顔かよ
We've got no choice.
仕方ない
We're going to have to resort to drastic measures.
ならこれからは強行策で行くしかないな
Drastic measures?
強行策
Shoma, I've been thinking.
前から思ってたんだが 晶馬
Your methods are too soft.
お前の遣り方は手緩いんだよ
Stop going along with the stalker chick's delusions,
ストーカー女の妄想なんかに一々付き合ってないで
and just grab what we need!
さっさと例の物を奪えばいいんだ
But...
でも
Her threat to incinerate the diary is just a bluff.
無理強いしたら燃やすなんてのはどうせ口先だけだ
She's just using your weakness to take advantage of you!
こっちの足元見て 言いようにされてるんだよ お前は
Taking it by force is not my style.
奪うって 気が進まないよ
What? Did you fall for that pervert girl or something?
何だ あの変態女に情でも湧いたのか
Huh?
ああ あるわけないじゃん
No way!
Are you really trying to save Himari?
そんなんで 本気でひまりを救う気があるのかよ
What about you?
兄貴こそ いつも何処で何遣ってんだか
What have you been doing all the time?
Hooking up with girls?
遊んでんじゃないのか
No fighting, guys!
喧嘩は駄目だよ お兄ちゃん
Himari, how long have you...?
ひまり 何時から
You'll get sick again if you...
おい はしゃぐとまた
Don't worry.
大丈夫 日頃の体力作りでこの通り
I'm all fine now thanks to daily workout!
But you two are never home lately.
だけど 二人ともこの頃いないこと多いから
I might get sick again from loneliness...
寂しくてまた倒れちゃうかも
Sorry, Himari!
御免な ひまり
We're not having fun without you-
俺たち遊んでるわけじゃ
Just kidding!
なんてな
Huh?
あれ どうしたの
What's wrong?
Just...
いいから
Wait in the living room!
居間で大人しくしてろ
You're both no fun.
ええ つれないのね
Anyway, if you fail again, I'll go and take it by force.
とにかく次失敗したら 俺が力ずくで奪う
ひまりのために
For Himari.
分かってる ひまりのために
I know.
For Himari.
わ ペンギンさんが一杯
Look! So many cute penguins!
皆こっち見てるぞ
They're all looking at you!
パパったら
Oh, honey.
Daddy, do you like penguins, too?
パパもペンギンさん好き
見て見て ペンギンさんがリンゴ持ってるよ
Look, the penguin is holding an apple!
You're right. It's like they're made just for you.
本当だ まるでリンゴのために作られたみたいだな
Please, Daddy!
ね パパ
Okay, we're getting matching straps for you, me, and mom!
よし パパとママとリンゴと三人でお揃いだ
Yay!
やったぁ パパ大好き
I love you, Daddy!
Moray Eel
Turtle
Of course, they're not selling those anymore.
同じのなんてもうあるわけないか
Over here!
おじちゃん 速く 速く
Don't run, Aoi!
駄目よ 藍 走らないの
Let her be for a while.
いいじゃないか 少しぐらい
Sheesh, you're too easy on her, Satoshi.
もう 聡さんったら 葵に甘いんだから
Daddy?
パパ
見て見て これ うつぼって言うの
Look, look!
It's called a moray eel!
Isn't it cute?
可愛いでしょう
Aren't you smart?
藍ちゃんは物知りだな
I love moray eels!
藍うつぼ大好き
I love moray eels, too.
おじさんも うつぼ大好きだよ
Yay!
やった
I like sea otters.
ママはラッコが好きよ
Did you know? There's a parents' day coming up at school.
あのね おじちゃん
藍今度授業参観があるんだぁ
皆パパも来るんだって
Everyone's daddies are coming.
I was wondering...
それでね お願いがあるの
藍　おじちゃんに来て欲しいの
if you could come?
Be my daddy.
ね 藍のパパになってよ
Hmm... well...
うん そうだな
We'll have to ask your mom.
それはママに聞かないと
M-Mr. Oginome?
荻 荻野目さん そんな
What do you... um...
あのう
Sorry for suddenly bringing this up at a place like this, but...
突然しかもこんな所で驚くかもしれないけど
I want you to have this.
これを 君に
Satoshi, is this...
聡さん これ
Would you seriously consider the three of us becoming a family?
三人で家族になるってことを真剣に考えてみてくれないかな
Yes. Gladly, if that's what you want.
はい 私たちなんかでよければ喜んで
はい やった 藍のパパだ
Yay!
You're my daddy now!
Congratulations!
おめでとう おめでとう
Thank you!
ありがとう
We...
僕たち
私たち
will live happily ever after!
幸せになります
How can...
そんな
パパの家族はあたしとママと
Mom and I are Daddy's family...
それ以外ありえないのに
No one else, yet...
やっぱりいくら頑張っても大切なものなんて
Are my precious things out of reach no matter how hard I-
Ow!
いったぁ
ジーザス
Jesus.
さあ これで分かったでしょう
Do you see it now?
勝つのは私
I will emerge victorious.
多蕗君と結ばれるのもこの私
I will also tie the knot with Tabuki.
No... my neck is tied up...
そんな結びりゃ
あ 首っくは
I won't let you!
そうはさせない
You hopeless maggot that doesn't know when to give up.
何処までも諦めの悪いしつこい蛆虫
More like a weed!
いえ まるで雑草ね
I'll pull out all your roots once and for all.
今度こそぺんぺん草も生えなくして差し上げてよ
Fool.
大馬鹿さん
It's...
まだよ まだ終わったわけじゃ　ない
It's not over yet!
ど どうして
H-How?!
I won't lose no matter how quickly you can draw.
あなたがどれだけ早打ちだろうと あたしは負けない
Because!
何故ならば
C-Could that be?!
そ それはまさか
What I have and you don't...
あたしにはあって あなたにはないもの それが運命
It's destiny!
As long as I hold this in my hands, our future will never budge!
これがある限り あたしたちの未来は変えられない
No!
I will end up with Tabuki!
多蕗さんと結ばれるのは　あたし
Yay!
やった 藍うつぼ大好き
I love moray eels!
I will be the one who attains the family!
家族を手に入れるのもこのあたし
I will accomplish Project M at all costs!
プロジェクトMは必ず成し遂げる
Destiny!
デスティニー
Yes, it will finally commence.
ええ とうとう実行するわ
Project M.
プロジェクトM 失敗は許されない
Failure is not an option.
嫌だわ
Gosh, it must...
はやく はやくすり潰さないと
It must be crushed soon.
ああ 疲れた
I'm beat!
二度目の引っ越しはさすがにきついなぁ
The second move is killing me!
あのさ
Say...
何
What?
やっぱりまだ日記は貸してもらえないよね
You're still not going to let me borrow the diary?
いいわよ 貸しても
I can let you borrow it.
What?!
本当にいいの
Really?
ただしこれからの用事が無事に済んだらね
Only if the next plan goes without a hitch.
The next plan?
これから
よし 出来た
Okay.
We're ready.
Thanks for carrying my stuff.
荷物運びご苦労様
I'll be going now.
じゃ あたしはここで
Uh... where are you going with such a big bag?
あのう そんなに荷物持って何処行くの
Where? I'm going to Tabuki and Yuri Tokikago's condo.
何処って
あたしはこれから多蕗さんと時籠百合のマンションに行くのよ
I got one of those postcards yesterday too.
そのハガキ 僕も昨日もらったんだよね
I think I have it on me...
たしかここに
もしかしてそれ お祝いのプレゼント とか
Wait, could that be a wedding present, by any chance?
I knew it!
やっぱり そうなんだ
Girls sure recover quickly from heartbreak!
さすが女の子は立ち直り速いな
I'll go with you to-
せっかくだし 僕も一緒にお祝いに
What are you babbling on about?
あたな 何寝言言ってんの
That woman is starting a national tour today, from Osaka.
あの女は今日から全国ツアーで大阪よ
That means, Tabuki is alone in the condo tonight.
つまり 今夜多蕗さんはマンションに独りきり
It's my last chance.
これがラストチャンスなの
Bye.
それじゃ
ええ ちょっと
Wait!
I can't believe it. She still hasn't given up?
まさか まだ諦めてなかったのか
プロジェクトM
Project M.
Mって いっそ多蕗と無理心中しよってんじゃん
"M"...
Don't tell me she's planning a double suicide with Tabuki?!
あの大事そうに抱えてる箱の中身は
Inside that box she's carrying so cautiously...
is...
中身は
まさか
Could it be?!
Noise makers not allowed
Sorry for barging in without notice.
突然押し掛けちゃって御免なさい
You just moved in too...
しかも 多蕗さん引っ越したばかりなのに
But I wanted to congratulate you as soon as possible!
でも はやくお祝いの言葉を言いたくて
It's all right. I'm glad you came!
いやぁ 来てくれて 嬉しいよ
I unpacked my things quicker than I'd expected, too.
荷物も案外早く片付いたしね
Although, it looks like it's going to be pouring in Tokyo tonight from the typhoon.
ただ台風の影響で東京も今夜は大雨らしいから
I'm worried about you getting home.
帰りが心配だな
Well then, I'll leave after a light celebration.
それなら ちょっとしたお祝いをしたら すぐお暇しますから
This place is huge!
広いよ
The floor's squeaky clean too!
床もずるずるだぁ
A celebrity's home sure is something else!
さすが芸能人の家は違うな
I wonder what Himari would say about this?
ひまりに見せたら何っていうかな
I'm glad you came too, Takakura.
高倉も来てくれて ありがとう
Wow, that thing is hanging from that place!
あんなとこにあんなのがぶら下がってるよ
I'm sorry, he followed me here...
Anyway, I put my heart into this for you two.
それより 多蕗さん
これ お二人のために心を込めて作ったんです
Please have it with Yuri, if you'd like.
よかったら 百合さんとどうぞ
What is it? I can't wait to see it!
ええ 何だろう ときめくなぁ
What?
何よ
Don't be reckless.
早まるなよ いざとなったら窓の外に投げるからね
I'll throw it out the window if I have to!
What are you talking about?
なんのことだか
It looks great!
これは凄いな
Did you make it yourself?
リンゴちゃんの手作りか
I hope it's to your liking.
お二人の口に合えばいいんですが
I wanted to share this with Yuri, but she just left for the national tour.
是非百合と一緒に頂きたかったけど
彼女つい先全国ツアーに行っちゃってさ
She'll be in Osaka for a while.
暫く大阪なんだ
Oh, no!
ええ それはがっかり
いいよ
It's all right.
Let's just eat it together.
せっかくだから 皆で頂こう
Oh! It's just an ordinary cake!
何だ 普通のケーキじゃないか
It's no ordinary cake.
普通じゃないわよ
It's my special curry-rice-shaped Mont Blanc, with love!
私の心のこもった特製カレー方モンブランよ
What was your problem, anyway?
あなた先から何なの
Nothing, I was just surprised you really came to congratulate them.
いいや ちゃんとお祝いする気だったんだと思って
あなたも よかったらケーキの感想聞かせてよ
Why don't you have a taste of my cake too?
それでは 僕たちの祝福のケーキをありがたく頂こうじゃないか
Well then, let's eat the congratulatory cake!
pwnt.
It kicked in faster than I'd expected.
思ったより早く効いたわね
この 眠気は 一体
Why do I feel so drowsy?
A blackout?
あれ 停電か
くそ 足が痺れて
Damn it, my legs are numb.
本当はこれだけは遣りたくなかった
I wish it didn't have to come to this.
多蕗さんに私を 私自身を愛して欲しかった
I wanted you to...
love me.
But I'm running out of time.
でも もう時間がない
Danger - Please do not imitate rapists.
もうすぐしたら 多蕗さんは目を覚ます
He'll wake up soon.
誰が誰だか区別も付かない状態で
While he can't recognize who he's with...
そう 今夜あたしは貴方の花嫁になるの
Yes...
I will become your bride tonight.
私としてではなく
Not as myself.
Hey... What are you doing...?
おい そこで 何を
薬の効きが悪かったみたいね
It looks like the drug didn't work as well on you.
いいわ せっかくだから教えてあげる
Oh, well. I'll let you in on my plan.
あたしたちの運命 プロジェクトMを
About our destiny, Project M.
What exactly is "M"?
ね Mって 一体
Pregnancy.
妊娠 マタニティーのMよ
"M" for "Maternity."
This is madness...
可笑しいよ
Was that written on your diary, too?
それも日記に書いてあることなのか
What exactly is that Fate Diary?
一体その運命日記って 書かれてることを無理やり本当の事にして
You're just going to forcibly execute what's written and call it destiny?
運命とか
That's nothing but a selfish delusion!
全部独りよがりの 妄想じゃないか
No, it's not a delusion...
違う これは妄想なんかじゃない
I have to do this, or our family will...
こうしないと あたしたち家族は
Whatever your reasons may be, this is just wrong!
どんな理由があろうと こんな遣り方間違ってる
Call it what you want.
だれが何を言われようと
I don't have any other choice!
あたしにはもうこれしかないの
So, leave me alone!
だから もう放っておいて
Destiny!
デスティニー
I can't leave you alone!
放っとけるかよ
What did you do that for?
ああ 何すんのよ
Huh?
あれ
Hallway
Lobby
I'm home, Tabuki!
ただいま 多蕗君
台風の影響でフライトがキャンセルに成っちゃった
My flight was canceled because of the typhoon.
明日一番の新幹線で行くことにしたわ
I decided to take the bullet train first thing tomorrow morning.
先の停電のせいかしら
I don't know if that blackout was to blame, but the electric lock won't open.
自動ロッカーが開かないの
開けてくれる
Can you open it for me?
ねぇ 多蕗君 聞こえてますか
Hey, Tabuki?
Can you hear me?
I was so close!
もう少しだったのに
これでよかったんだよ
It was for the better.
That wasn't what you wanted to do.
あんなこと 君のためにも よくないよ
What do you know about me?
あなたにあたしの何が分かるって言うの
あたしが代わりに多蕗さんの子供を生む
I must bear Tabuki's child in her place.
そうしないと 運命の輪は繋がらない
Otherwise, the circle of fate wouldn't be complete.
これが最後のチャンスだったのに
It was my last chance!
あのさ 君は多蕗や百合さんの気持ちはどうでもいいの
You don't care about Tabuki and Yuri's feelings, then?
違う
Hold on! Tabuki being with her was a mistake in the first place!
多蕗さんとあの女が一緒にいる事がそもそもの間違いなのよ
Your heart is pitch black, darker than any girl I've ever known!
君は僕が今まで遇ったどの女の子よりも 心が真っ黒だ
How dare you! You don't even know anything.
何よ　何も知らないくせに
I don't want to know.
知りたくもないね
You act all innocent, but can you honestly say you care about your sister?
平和そうな顔して
貴方だって兄弟の気持ちを考えてるって言えるの
What are you talking about?
何の事だよ
I can tell by just looking at Himari.
ひまりちゃんを見てれば分かる
Aren't you just trying to maintain the facade of a happy family to make yourself feel better?
貴方は自分の都合のいいように表面的に家族の形を取り繕っているだけじゃないの
Whatever.
もういいのよ これからは一人でやる
I'll do everything by myself from now on.
The circle won't be complete unless I work hard and become Momoka.
私が頑張って桃果に成らなきゃ 輪が繋がらない
At this rate, my mom and dad will stay apart.
このままじゃ ママもパパもバラバラ
The family will be broken into pieces.
家族が弾け飛んでしまう
The family?
家族
そうよ これはすべて家族のため
Yes, it's all for the family.
It's my duty, the reason I was born.
私の義務 生まれてきた意味
It has nothing to do with how I feel.
私の気持ちとは関係ない
Then, Tabuki isn't...
じゃ 多蕗の事は
I like him. I love him!
好きよ
愛してるわ
だって 桃果がそうだったんだもの
Because... Momoka did.
Huh?
桃果って 亡くなったお姉さんの事だろう
Momoka is your late sister, right?
何言ってんだ
What are you saying?
Like I said, it doesn't concern you.
あなたとは関係ないって言ったでしょう
Hold on!
ちょっと 待てよ
No! Let go!
嫌だ 放して
Oh, no!
大変
Your heart is pitch black!
君は心が真っ黒だ
Why?
どうして
What happened?
何だ
Hey!
おい
Even if Your Love is a Lie, I...
subete ga moshi kimerarete tara
If everything was written in stone
全てがもし
決められてたら
bokura wa doushite mogaku no darou
Why have we been resisting our fate?
僕らはどうして
もがくのだろう
sore wa kimi ja nai
It's not you
それは君じゃない
kimi no sei ja nai
It's not your fault
君のせいじゃない
kanashimi wa mou takusan nanda
I've had enough misery
悲しみはもう沢山なんだ
dakara sou ja nai
You're mistaken
だからそうじゃない
今のままじゃない
ima no mama ja nai
Fate can be changed
umaku tsutaekirenai kedo
I can't explain it, but
うまく伝えきれないけど
Dear my future
Dear your future
Because those two were my true friends back then.
だって あの時二人は本当に友達だったから
So, I'm rooting for you from the bottom of my heart, even now.
だから 今でも心から応援してるよ
Lily Hoshino
生存戦略 モンブラン